{
    "subject": "resource/Cycling_at_the_1992_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Men's_team_time_trial",
    "predicate": "ontology/goldMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Bernd_Dittert",
    "human_readable": "Bernd Dittert was the gold medalist in men's team time trial at the 1992 Summer Olympics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9734982252120972,
            "question": "Who won the gold medal in the men's team time trial at the 1992 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9343945384025574,
            "question": "In which year did Bernd Dittert win his Olympic gold medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9022886157035828,
            "question": "What event did Bernd Dittert win a gold medal in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.803630530834198,
            "question": "Was Bernd Dittert an individual or team competitor at the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7287905216217041,
            "question": "What type of Olympics did Bernd Dittert participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7284569144248962,
            "question": "Can you name another athlete who won a gold medal at the 1992 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3834860920906067,
            "question": "What is the significance of winning a gold medal in the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18506021797657013,
            "question": "What other sports are featured at the Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1349666714668274,
            "question": "What is the difference between individual and team competitions in the Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.019930105656385422,
            "question": "Name a cycling event that involves teams."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bernd Dittert was the gold medalist in men's team time trial at the 1992 Summer Olympics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7364_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the difference between individual and team competitions in the Olympics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7364_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other sports are featured at the Summer Olympics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7364_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of winning a gold medal in the Olympics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7364_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7364_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Bernd Dittert, along with Christian Meyer, Uwe Peschel, and Michael Rich, won the gold medal in the men's team time trial event at the 1992 Summer Olympics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Bernd Dittert, along with Christian Meyer, Uwe Peschel, and Michael Rich, won a gold medal in the men's team time trial at the 1992 Summer Olympics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}